Paul Calnan

WEB DEVELOPER

Contact

0447 226 550

paulwritescode@gmail.com https://github.com/PaulCalnan https://www.linkedin.com/in/paulcalnan

Education

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Web Development Immersive March 2021 - June 2021

CODER ACADEMY

Software Development Course February 2017 - March 2017

Tools used

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Express
- React
- PostgreSQL
- HTML 5
- Ruby on Rails
- CSS 3

- ¡Query
- Vue.js
- Cloudinary
- Heroku
- MongoDB
- SQLite
- Git
- Sinatra

About

Early in life my innate technical curiosity showed through in my hobbies that were always technical pursuits.

On finishing high school I was given the opportunity to work within the electrical industry which continued to satisfy my strong interest in technology for many years.

During that time I have developed a broad set of transferable skills. Leveraging these abilities coupled with my desire to learn new things allows me to hit the ground running, as I up-skill into software engineering.

Experience

QUICK ELECTRICS

Self Employed Electrician 2015 - Present

- Project management from design to completion
- Team leadership and mentorship to apprentices
- Tactful and patient communicator
- Effective problem solving skills in complex systems
- Ability to work pro-actively in a team or independent
- High standard towards attention to detail

ELECTRONICS TECHNICIAN

CEA Technologies

2013 - 2015

- · Electronic assembly, modification and repair
- Precise work under microscope to high standards
- · Meticulous attention to detail
- Work within teams under direction from Engineers
- · Conform to design documentation and drawings

ELECTRONICS TECHNICIAN

Fire Control Systems

2012 - 2013

- Electronic assembly of military remote weapon systems
- Precise work under microscope to high standards
- Test and calibration completed units
- Work within teams under direction from Engineers
- · Conform to design documentation and drawings

Skills and Abilities

- · Calm under pressure
- · Ability to adapt to challenges
- Strong attention to detail
- · Effective team collaborator
- · Excellent communication skills
- Focussed work ethic